whosoff.com 2014-06-19

# Privacy Policy | WhosOff and the WhosOff.com Service

###  PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE USING OUR SITE

X:drive Computing Limited (we) are committed to protecting and respecting the privacy of our customers, their staff and other guest users of our site.

This policy (together with our [Terms of Website Use](http://www.whosoff.com/terms-of-use/)  and [Cookie Policy](http://www.whosoff.com/cookie_policy/) ) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us.  Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. By visiting www.whosoff.com (our site) you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy. 

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the Act), the data controller is X:drive Computing Limited, a company registered in England and Wales with company number 03736333 whose registered office is at 2nd Floor Rear Office, 29-30 Watling Street, Canterbury, Kent, CT1 2UD.  Please note though that if you are a staff member of one of our customers, your employer is the data controller for the purposes of the Act and we merely process the data on their behalf as part of your and their use of our services.

#### INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU

We may collect and process the following data about you:

• Information you give us. 

You may give us information about you by filling in forms on our site or by corresponding with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise. This includes information you provide when you subscribe to the Whos Off service and use such service, sign up to our mailing list, participate in social media functions on our site and when you report a problem with our site or provide other feedback to us.  The information you give us may include your name, address, e-mail address and phone number, any optional details you choose to add to the “edit my details” area of our site, and staff leave information relating to holiday, sickness and other absences. 

• Information we collect about you. 

With regard to each of your visits to our site we may automatically collect the following information:

• technical information, including the internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform; 

• information about your visit, including the full uniform resource locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from our site (including date and time); information you viewed or searched for; page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page and any phone number used to contact us. 

• Information we receive from other sources. 

We may work with third parties (including, for example, business partners, sub-contractors, advertising networks, analytics providers, search information providers, credit reference agencies) and may receive information about you from them.

#### COOKIES

Cookies are small pieces of information stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive.  Our site uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our site. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our site and also allows us to improve our site. For detailed information on the cookies we use and the purposes for which we usethem see our[Cookie Policy.](http://www.whosoff.com/cookie_policy/)

#### USES MADE OF THE INFORMATION

We use information held about you in the following ways:

• Information you give to us.

We will use this information:

• to correspond with you and to provide any information you may request from us;

• to process your organisation’s application to use our services and carry out our obligations under any contract;

• to register each staff member as a user and process all requests, approvals, declines, sickness, out of office and meeting information;

• to deal with any enquiries, problems or complaints you may have about our services or our site;

• to provide you with information about other services we may offer that are similar to those that you have already ordered or enquired about;

• to notify you about changes to our service;

• to ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer. 

We may also use your information to provide you with information about goods or services we feel may interest you. If you are, or have been, a customer of ours we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale or negotiations of a sale to you. Otherwise we will only contact you by electronic means for marketing purposes if you have expressly consented to this.

If you are a staff member of one of our customers your personal data entered into the “enter my details” area of our site will not be used for marketing purposes and will only be shared with other members of your organisation in accordance with this policy.

• Information we collect about you. 

We will use this information:

• to administer our site and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;

• to improve our site to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer; 

• to allow you to participate any interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so;

• as part of our efforts to keep our site safe and secure;

• to measure or understand the effectiveness any advertising we may serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you;

• Information we receive from other sources. 

We may combine this information with information you give to us and information we collect about you. We may us this information and the combined information for the purposes set out above (depending on the types of information we receive).

#### DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

Whilst using our services, other members of your organisation who wish to contact you will be able to identify you by your name and any other personal information you may make available about yourself on the “edit my details” page of our site.  Please note we have no responsibility or control over the contents of any communications made between members of your organisation whilst using our services.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties including:

• To suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance of any contract we enter into with them or you.

• To credit reference agencies for the purpose of assessing your credit score where this is a condition of us entering into a contract with you.

• In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.

• If X:drive Computing Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.

• If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Website [Terms of use](http://www.whosoff.com/terms-of-use/)  or [Terms and Conditions](http://www.whosoff.com/terms_and_conditions/) of Supply and any other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of X:drive Computing Limited, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

We may also share anonymised aggregate information about our users, for example the number of users of our website or services on a given day, however we do not share personal information with third parties for marketing purposes.

#### WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATA

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area. It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things,  the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing..

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers which only a limited number of our employees and sub-contractors can access.  All information transmitted will be encrypted using SSL technology.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

#### YOUR RIGHTS

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. You can exercise this right at any time by contacting us at support@whosoff.com.

We do not share personal information with third parties for marketing purposes.

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates.  If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies.  Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

 **ACCESS TO INFORMATION**

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

As a staff member of one of our customers you may access the personal information stored about you through the “edit my details” area of our site.  It is your responsibility to ensure the personal information stored about you is correct and up-to-date at all times.

#### CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

Any changes we may make to this policy in the future will be posted on this page. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to this policy.

#### CONTACT

Questions, comments and requests regarding this policy are welcomed and should be addressed to support@whosoff.com.

Thank you for visiting our site.

**Not sure whether WhosOff is right for your company?**  
From carpet fitters to blue chip household names, with over 65,000 members why not let our users tell you all about it.  

**Stay in touch**  
Stay up to date with our latest features and more.
